<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pakhi\'s Portfolio</string>

    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="default_error">Error!!</string>
    <string name="default_text">Default text</string>
    <string name="default_long_text">He found what he was looking for in his inside pocket. It seemed to be a
silver cigarette lighter. He flicked it open, held it up in the air, and
clicked it. The nearest street lamp went out with a little pop. He
clicked it again — the next lamp flickered into darkness. Twelve times
he clicked the Put-Outer, until the only lights left on the whole street
were two tiny pinpricks in the distance, which were the eyes of the cat
watching him. If anyone looked out of their window now, even beady-eyed
Mrs. Dursley, they wouldn\'t be able to see anything that was happening
down on the pavement. Dumbledore slipped the Put-Outer back inside his
cloak and set off down the street toward number four, where he sat down
on the wall next to the cat.</string>
    <string name="list_topic">Pakhi\'s showcase</string>
    <string name="my_name">Pakhi</string>
    <string name="introduction_line">\"I have found art in science and science in art\"</string>
    <string name="introduction_card_line">\"My dream is to create!\n
        Putting pieces of my soul into my work\"</string>

    <string name="skills_card_line">\"10000 hours\n
        of effort creates 10 seconds of magic.\"</string>

    <string name="interests_card_line">\"Did we even live\n
        if our eyes didn\'t fill up with emotions sometimes!\"</string>

    <string name="contact_card_line">\"If you would like\n
        me to work for you, I\'d love to hear from you!\"</string>
    
    <string name="interests_creative_arts">I\'ve always loved deep discussions about literature, evenings filled with music and
        rooms filled with art. The process of creating stories, music, movies, art is fascinating to me.
        That\'s why I like software development so much. It lets me create usable art.</string>
    
    <string name="interests_travel">A human mind is extremely noisy most of the time. There are certain times, though,
        when it shuts down and just absorbs without analysis. For most people, sports does that. For me, travel brings that freedom.</string>
    
    <string name="interests_food">The quantity of what I eat is never a lot, but I love trying diverse kinds of food.
        The rich aroma of eastern spices, the bland but alluring taste of western cheese, there must be a reason
        why nature gave us a sense of taste.</string>
    
    <string name="skills_android">I\'ve been working on Android app development since last 3 years and have been programming for 12 years.
        Most of the apps I\'ve developed were for TCS where I worked for 2 years. Access to those is not possible, thus I made
        this app as a showcase. Everything from design, development to performance testing of this app is done by me
        and I put a lot of importance on maintainability of the code. So, apart from giving high performance,
        my code is architecturally sound.</string>
    <string name="skills_spring">I make my server-side using Spring framework and use Docker to deploy the code.
        I\'m comfortable with frontend-server integration, file operations, db operations and social authentications.
        For the server-side, speed is the most important aspect. I ensure it with continuous research into latest
        improvements and optimizing my code.</string>
    <string name="skills_node">I make my server-side using Node.js and use Google cloud to deploy the code.
        I\'m comfortable with frontend-server integration, file operations, db operations and social authentications.
        For the server-side, speed is the most important aspect. I ensure it with continuous research into latest
        improvements and optimizing my code.</string>
    <string name="skills_others">I have done some minor works on web development, machine learning and augmented reality.
        I\'ve gone through the background aspects of these technologies, such as understanding how machine learning algorithms work.
        However, my interest lies more in using those algorithms to solve user-level problems.
        I plan to develop these skills in the future.</string>

    <string name="main_activity_info">I\'m calling this app my showcase because my other apps are not public. I\'ve shown a small preview of
    how my apps tend to feel. You\'ll notice the performance of the app is high even with high resolution images. Each transition,
    click, swipe action is added while keeping performance in mind.</string>
    
    <string name="introduction_activity_info">Notice that the design is logical and the gist of the page can be understood
        at a glance without reading a lot because of the graphs. The design is different for older phones and landscape mode.</string>
    
    <string name="skills_activity_info">The pie chart is a custom component i.e. it\'s created from scratch unlike
        let\'s say a button which is provided by the Android framework. It fits with the logic
        of showing my strongest skills in one place, as well as showing my capability of creating custom components when needed.</string>

    <string name="interests_activity_info">I kept this page a bit glamorous because it shows my interest in bringing challenging
        designs to life. The design and the positions of the images were a challenge. There was also a lot of struggle and
        calculation involved in ensuring the correct item moves to the center on click.</string>

    <string name="contact_hint">I would love to develop apps for you, please message me here…</string>

    <string name="transition_name_image_launcher">imageSplash</string>

    <string name="transition_name_image_view_design_item">imageViewDesignItem%d</string>
    <string name="transition_name_image_view_design_item_container">imageViewDesignItemContainer%d</string>
    <string name="transition_name_text_view_design_item_title">textViewDesignItemTitle%d</string>
    <string name="transition_name_text_view_design_item_heart">textViewDesignItemHeart%d</string>

    <string name="transition_name_text_item_profile_introduction">textItemProfileIntroduction%d</string>
    <string name="transition_name_image_item_profile_introduction">imageItemProfileIntroduction%d</string>
    <string name="transition_name_image_bg_item_profile_introduction">imageBgItemProfileIntroduction%d</string>

    <string name="transition_name_image_view_skills">imageViewSkills</string>
    <string name="transition_name_text_view_skills">textViewSkills</string>
    <string name="transition_name_image_view_skills_container">imageViewSkillsContainer</string>

    <string name="transition_name_text_view_contact">textViewContact</string>
</resources>
